Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Research Program Files
  - Subseries C. Turned-down proposals
    - Subsubseries 2. Turned-down files, 1981 - 1988
      - T537, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Dec. 1983 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - T538, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1983 (Box 143, Folder 18)
      - T539, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1983 (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - T540, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Sept. 1983 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - T541, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Sept. 1983 (Box 143, Folder 21)
      - T541, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - T541, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - T541b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-July 1984 (Box 143, Folder 24)
      - T541b, Proposal attachments, Feb. 1984 (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - T542, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - T543, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1983-July 1984 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - T544, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - T545, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - T546, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - T547, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Oct. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - T548, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - T549, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - T551, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1983-May 1984 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - T552, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - T553, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - T555, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - T556, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - T557, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - T558, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - T559, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983-July 1984 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - T560, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - T561, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - T562, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - T563, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 20)
      - T564, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      - T565b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1986-Feb. 1987 (Box 144, Folder 22)
      - T567, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - T568, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 144, Folder 24)
      - T569, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - T570, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      - T571, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Oct. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 27)
      - T572, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 144, Folder 28)
      - T573, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - T574, Proposal, notes and correspondence,Oct. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - T577, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - T578, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - T579, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - T580, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - T581, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - T582, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983-Mar. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - T582, Proposal attachments, Nov. 1983 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - T583, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1983-Mar. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - T584, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - T585, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - T586, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - T587, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - T588, Proposal and notes, Nov. 1983, Mar. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - T591, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983-Dec. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - T593, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - T594, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar., July 1984 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - T594, Proposal attachment Mar. 1983: MIT Research Laboratory of Electronics. Quarterly Progress Report #56, Jan. 1960Mar. 1983 (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - T594, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 1)
      - T594, Proposal, notes and correspondence,Dec. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 2)
      - T595, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 3)
      - T596, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 4)
      - T597, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 5)
      - T598, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 6)
      - T599, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-July 1984 (Box 146, Folder 7)
      - T601, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983 (Box 146, Folder 8)
      - T602, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 9)
      - T603, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 10)
      - T604, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 11)
      - T605, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Aug. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 12)
      - T605, Proposal attachments: Background information #1 (Box 146, Folder 13)
      - T605, Proposal attachments: Background information #2 (Box 146, Folder 14)
      - T606a, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Mar. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 15)
      - T606b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-July 1984 (Box 146, Folder 16)
      - T606b, Photos: artwork and exhibition, 1982-1983 (Box 146, Folder 17)
      - T606b, Slides: artwork and exhibition, 1982-1983 (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - T607, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983 (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - T608, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan. 1984 (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - T609, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Jan. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - T610, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - T611, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-July 1984 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - T613, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - T614, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - T615, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - T616, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-July 1983 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - T616, Background information (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - T617, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - T618, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - T620, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - T621, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - T622a, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb.-June 1984 (Box 147, Folder 13)
      - T623, Proposal, notes and correspondence,Jan.-Mar. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - T624, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-June 1984 (Box 147, Folder 15)
      - T624, Proposal attachments #1 (Box 147, Folder 16)
      - T624, Proposal attachments #2 (Box 147, Folder 17)
      - T624, Proposal attachments #3 (Box 147, Folder 18)
      - T625, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 19)
      - T627, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-June 1984 (Box 147, Folder 20)
      - T628, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 21)
      - T628b, Proposal and notes, Mar.-Aug. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 22)
      - T629, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 23)
      - T630[a,b], Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-May. 1984 (Box 147, Folder 24)
      - T631, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-July 1984 (Box 147, Folder 25)
      - T632, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-June 1984 (Box 147, Folder 26)
      - T632b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept. 1984-Feb. 1985 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - T634, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - T634, Background information #1 (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - T634, Background information #2 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - T635, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - T636, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - T637, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 7)
      - T638, Background information and notes, Feb.-July 1984 (Box 148, Folder 8)
      - T639, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 9)
      - T640, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 10)
      - T641, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 148, Folder 11)
      - T642, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb.-July 1984 (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - T642, Psychoacoustics and Speech Processing for a Modiolar Auditory Prosthesis, Matthew Kent Herndon, 1981 (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - T642, Design and Fabrication of an Implantable Multichannel Neural Stimulator, Mani Soma, 1980 (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - T642, Speech Processor Design Considerations for an Auditory Prosthesis, Les Eugene Atlas, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - T642, The Design and Fabrication of Microelectrode Arrays for Cochlear Prosthesis, Shihab Ahmed Shamma (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - T643, The Design and Fabrication of Microelectrode Arrays for Cochlear Prosthesis, Shihab Ahmed Shamma, Feb. 1984 (Box 149, Folder 6)
      - T644a, The Design and Fabrication of Microelectrode Arrays for Cochlear Prosthesis, Shihab Ahmed Shamma, Feb.-July 1984 (Box 149, Folder 7)
      - T644a, Background information "A" #1 (Box 149, Folder 8)
      - T644a, Background information "A" #2 (Box 149, Folder 9)
      - T644a, Background information "B" #1 (Box 149, Folder 10)
      - T644a, Background information "B" #2 (Box 149, Folder 11)
      - T644a, Background information "B" #3 (Box 149, Folder 12)
      - T644a, Background information "B" #4 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - T644a, Background information "C" (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - T644b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - T645, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb.-Mar. 1984 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - T646, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - T647, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-May 1984 (Box 150, Folder 6)
      - T647, Proposal and notes, Feb. 1984 (Box 150, Folder 7)
      - T648, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb.-July 1984 (Box 150, Folder 8)
      - T648, Proposal attachments #1 (Box 150, Folder 9)
      - T648, Proposal attachments #2 (Box 150, Folder 10)
      - T649, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb.-Mar. 1984 (Box 150, Folder 11)
      - T651, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-May 1984 (Box 150, Folder 12)
      - T651, Background information #1 (Box 150, Folder 13)
      - T651, Background information #2 (Box 150, Folder 14)
      - T651, Background information #3 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Table of Contents and Introduction to Part I, copy 1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Part 1, Section I, copy 1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Part 1, Section II, copy 1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Parts II and III, copy 1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Table of Contents and Part I, Section I, copy 2,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Part I, Section II-Part III, copy 2,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packets B, C,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet for x.1, "Indexing and Classification",Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-1, Vitae,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 12)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-1, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 151, Folder 13)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-1, Relevant papers #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-2,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-2, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-2, Relevant papers, #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-3,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet A-3, Relevant papers,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet B-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet B-1, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet B-1, Relevant papers #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet B-2,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project Packet B-2, Relevant papers,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 11)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet C-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 152, Folder 12)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet C-1, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 1)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet C-1, Relevant papers #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet X-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet X-1, Relevant papers,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-1, Relevant papers,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-2,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 7)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-2, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-2, Relevant papers #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 9)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-3 #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 10)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Y-3 #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 11)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Z-1,Apr. 1984 (Box 153, Folder 12)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Z-1, Relevant papers #1,Apr. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - T651, Proposal version 7. Project packet Z-1, Relevant papers #2,Apr. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - T651b, Abbreviated proposal, version 1, June 1984 (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - T651b, Correspondence, June-Nov. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - T652, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - T653, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - T654, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Dec. 1983-July 1984 (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - T654, Background information (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - T655, Proposal notes and correspondence, Mar. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - T656, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 10)
      - T657, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 11)
      - T658, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1984 (Box 154, Folder 12)
      - T659, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-July 1984 (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - T660, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-July 1984 (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - T661, Proposal and notes, Nov. 1983-July 1984 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      - T661, Background information: Ph.D. Thesis, preliminary draft (Box 155, Folder 4)
      - T661, Background information: Ph.D. Thesis. (Box 155, Folder 5)
      - T662, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Aug. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 1)
      - T663, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 2)
      - T664, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 3)
      - T665, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-June 1984 (Box 156, Folder 4)
      - T666, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 5)
      - T667, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - T668, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - T669, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 8)
      - T670, Documents and correspondence, May-June 1984 (Box 156, Folder 9)
      - T670, Documents and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 10)
      - T670, Documents and correspondence, Feb.-Mar. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 11)
      - T670, Documents and correspondence, Jan. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 12)
      - T670, Documents and correspondence, Sept.-Oct. 1983 (Box 156, Folder 13)
      - T670, Notes, c. Apr.-May 1984 (Box 156, Folder 14)
      - T670, "Xanadu" program, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 15)
      - T671, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 16)
      - T672, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 17)
      - T673, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-June 1984 (Box 156, Folder 18)
      - T674, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr. 1984 (Box 156, Folder 19)
      - T676, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-June 1984 (Box 156, Folder 20)
      - T678, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-July 1984 (Box 156, Folder 21)
      - T679, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - T680, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - T681, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 3)
      - T682, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-July 1984 (Box 157, Folder 4)
      - T683, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - T684, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - T685, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May.-July 1984 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - T686, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - T688, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - T689, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - T690, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May-July 1984 (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - T691, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May.-July 1984 (Box 157, Folder 12)
      - T692, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 13)
      - T693, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May.-June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 14)
      - T694, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May 1984 (Box 157, Folder 15)
      - T695, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May-July 1984 (Box 157, Folder 16)
      - T695, Proposal attachments (Box 157, Folder 17)
      - T696, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 18)
      - T697, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 19)
      - T697, Proposal attachments #1 (Box 157, Folder 20)
      - T697, Proposal attachments #2 (Box 157, Folder 21)
      - T698, Proposal attachments, May-June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 22)
      - T699, Proposal attachments, June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 23)
      - T700, Proposal attachments, June 1984 (Box 157, Folder 24)
      - T701, Proposal attachments, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - T701, Proposal attachments: Book draft, Ch.1-2 (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - T701, Proposal attachments: Book draft, Ch. 3-6 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - T701, Proposal attachments: Book draft, Ch. 7-8 (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - T701, Proposal attachments: Book draft, Ch. 9-10 (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - T702, Proposal, notes and correspondence,May-Oct. 1984 (Box 158, Folder 6)
      - TT703, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1984 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      - T704, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 8)
      - T705, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 9)
      - T706, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 10)
      - T707, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 11)
      - T708, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 12)
      - T709, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 13)
      - T710, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 14)
      - T711, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 15)
      - T712, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 16)
      - T712, Proposal attachments (Box 158, Folder 17)
      - T713, T714, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-July 1984 (Box 158, Folder 18)
      - T715, Proposal, notes and correspondence,July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - T716, T717, Proposal, notes and correspondence,July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 2)
      - T719, Proposal, notes and correspondence,July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - T720, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - T721, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - T722, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 6)
      - T723, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 7)
      - T724, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1981-Feb. 1982, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 8)
      - T725, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 9)
      - T726, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July 1984 (Box 159, Folder 10)
      - T727, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 11)
      - T728, Proposal, notes and correspondence, July-Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 12)
      - T729, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Oct.-Nov. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 13)
      - T730, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Nov. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 14)
      - T731, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 15)
      - T732, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug.-Sept. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 16)
      - T733, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1982, Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 17)
      - T734, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar. 1982, Aug. 1984 (Box 159, Folder 18)
      - T735, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1982, Aug. 1984 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - T736, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Sept.-Oct. 1984 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - T736, Movement Notation, Noa Eshkol and Abraham Wachmann, 1958 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - T736, Movement Notations, Part Two, Noa Eshkol and Michael Shoshani, 1982 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - T737, Language of Shape and Movement, John G. Harries, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 5)